Agustín Noé FIORDELISI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



- +54 261 567 8819
- Mendoza province, Argentina
- agulirio@yahoo.com.ar
- in www.linkedin.com/in/agustinfiordelisi

SKILLS

Java – Spring

Node.js

SQL & NoSQL

Angular 8

Git & Jira

Scrum and Agile Method

LANGUAGE

✓ English: Upper Intermediate

✓ German : Low

INTERESTS

- o 3D Printing
- o Mechatronics enthusiast
- Sports Athletic

PROFILE

Since my teenhood I always found myself linked to the technological world with PC assembly and repair. In high school I started with basic concepts of lineal programming in CNC and then logic adapted to automated systems, PLC. For many years I put it aside, but in 2018 I wanted to return to the technological world but hand in hand with development, I studied at EGG Tech and took several courses related to software development and programming of microcontrollers. I am currently studying and will continue to do so, since I considerer that throughout life we are able to continue learning.

My strengths:

- Ability to lern new knowledge
- Ability to teach and group management
- I am a dedicated person
- I consider myself a calm and thinking person

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EGG Education
Finished in December 2018

DEGREE IN PHYSICAL EDUCATION TEACHER

University of Aconcagua Finished in July 2018

ELECTROMECHANICAL TECHNICIAN

Technical School – Ing. Pablo Nogues 4-111 Finished in December

WORK EXPERIENCE

QUINTO IMPACTO | DEVELOPER

Febr. 2019 – Present | Mendoza, Arg. Developer of "PUPILINK" and "MapUNCu"

UNIVERSITY OF ACONCAGUA | TEACHER

March. 2017 - Present | Mendoza, Arg. Biomechanic professor in the Degree in Physical Education.

EGG TECH | TEACHER

Oct. 2019 - Present | Mendoza, Arg. Professor in programming course.

EGG TECH | DEVELOPER

Aug. 2020 - Present | Mendoza, Arg. Backend developer in Egg's APP